{
  "name": "Additions Recap Exercise",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "6,416 + 3,254 = ?",
      "answers": ["9,670"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "2,708 + 5,142 = ?",
      "answers": ["7,850"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "2,913 + 5,668 = ?",
      "answers": ["8,581"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "3,549 + 2,843 + 1,564 = ?",
      "answers": ["7,956"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "6,018 + 1,625 + 1,804 = ?",
      "answers": ["9,447"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "5,632 + 1 = ?",
      "answers": ["5,633"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "7,489 + 10 = ?",
      "answers": ["7,499"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "9,652 + 100 = ?",
      "answers": ["9,752"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "2,586 + 1000 = ?",
      "answers": ["3,586"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the missing addend:\n800 + ____ = 1,500",
      "answers": ["700"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the missing addend:\n2,500 + ____ = 6,000",
      "answers": ["3,500"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the missing addend:\n300 + ____ + 300 = 1,800",
      "answers": ["1,200"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the missing addend:\n3,500 + ____ + 1,000 = 9,000",
      "answers": ["4,500"],
      "keyboard": "digits_comma_only",
      "timeout": 180
    }
  ]
}